Hi there.
It's only about a week before Christmas,
*singing* "Tis the season to be jolly and joyus! With a burst of pleasure we feel it alright. Fa la la! It's the season when the saints can employ us. To spread the news about peace and to keep love alive!"
and some of you are no doubt scrambling to determine what might make an appropriate Christmas gift.
As you may know, or also may not,
I have written a book that's coming out in January - on January 23rd as a matter of fact,
called "12 Rules for Life, An Antidote to Chaos".
And it's possible that some of the people you know might be interested in receiving that as a gift.
However, a promise to get a book a month later doesn't make a great Christmas gift, exactly.
So what I've done is put together a small package that announces that the book has been ordered,
that has a short letter in it from me and also that contains the introduction to the book;
about 10 pages which I called "Overture".
You could order the book online from any of the vendors to whom I have provided a link in the description of the video.
And you could also download the package I have produced
and print it out to make the gift more tangible and therefor more, well, solid and appreciated I would say.
And then you could put it in an envelope and you can give that little package as a gift.
And maybe that would be more appropriate than a mere indication that the book is on its way.
So, I hope that's useful. Thank you all for tuning in over the last year and before that.
And for all the support you've offered me in the last year.
And Merry Christmas and Happy New Year.
"Tis the season to be jolly and joyous."
"Fa la la!"
"With a burst of pleasure, we feel it all right."
"It's the season when the saints can employ us."
"Fa la la!"
"To spread the news about peace and to keep love alive..."